History Department Faculty (Susanne P. Lloyd) Records 1950-1976
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
History Department Faculty (Susanne P. Lloyd) Records
1950-1976
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Archives 9
3.5 linear feet
These records, from the office of Dr. Susanne P. Lloyd, relate to her work as a member and/or advisor to various campus organizations such as ASWSU, Koinonia House, NOW, North American Indian Students Association, Washington State Women's Council, and WSC Commission on the Status of Women.
These records relate to her work as a member and/or advisor to various campus organizations such as ASWSU, Koinonia House, NOW, North American Indian Students Association, Washington State Women's Council, and WSC Commission on the Status of Women.
The Collection is open for research use.
On December 8, 1976, Bruce C. Harding accessioned these records from the office of Dr. Susanne P. Lloyd who had passed away while on leave (see Pullman Herald, November 24, 1976). Dr. Raymond Muse, Chairman, Department of History, approved the acquisition.
Lloyd, Susanne P.
Washington State University. Dept. of History. Faculty (Susanne P. Lloyd)--Archives; State College of Washington. Dept. of History. W; Washington State University. Dept. of History. Faculty (Susanne P. Lloyd)--Records and correspondence
Universities and colleges--Faculty--Women; Universities and colleges--Societies, etc.
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities; Women
- Susanne P. Lloyd - Personal Data and Talks, 1944-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ASWSU - Ad Hoc Committee on Effectiveness, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ASWSU - Student Ombudsmen, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ASWSU - Undergraduate Student Affairs Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ASWSU - Student Activities Board, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Koinonia House, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Koinonia House, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6a)
- Koinonia House, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6b)
- Day Care Data, 1971; 73 items (Box 2, Folder 1)
- University Senate, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Faculty Affairs, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- WSU - Commission on the Status of Women, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Woman in American Society - University 300, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- National Organization for Women, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Association of American Colleges - Project on Status and Education of Women, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Washington State Women's Council, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Selected Term Papers and Studies, 1960-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Tape recording- Women's Liberation: Whim or Revolution?, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Tape recordings- Women's Opportunity Development Seminar, Idaho Falls, AEC, July 31, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Experimental Education Program - History (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Women's Data, 1959-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Women's Data, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1a)
- Women's Data, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1b)
- Women's Data, 1965-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1c)
- Women's Data, 1963-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1d)
- Women's Data, 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Women's Data, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Women's Data, 1963-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Women's Data, 1954-1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- North American Indian Students Association, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Indian Conference - WSU, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Indian Education, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Indian Education, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Committee on Discriminatory Practices, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- WSU - Admissions Folder, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Publications re: Women's Activities (Box 7)
  - Bird, Caroline. Everything a Woman Needs to Know to Get Paid What She's Worth., 1974
  - Bird, Caroline. Born Female., 1971
  - Bullough, Vern L. The Subordinate Sex; A History of Attitudes Toward Women., 1974
  - Firestone. Shulamith. The Dialectic of Sex; the Case for Feminist Revolution., 1972
  - Grummon, Donald L. and Andrew M. Barclay. Sexuality, A Search for Perspective., 1971
  - Harbeson, Gladys E. Choice and Challenge for the American Woman., 1967
  - Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conference. Women's Higher Education: Some Unanswered Questions., 1973
  - Lader, Lawrence. Abortion., 1966
  - Millett, Kate. Sexual Politics., 1971
  - Morgan. Robin (ed.) Sisterhood Is Powerful., 1970
  - Salper, Roberta (ed.) Female Liberation; History and Current Politics., 1972
  - Schneir, Miriam (ed.) Feminism: The Essential Historical Writings., 1972
  - Scott, Anne F. and Andrew M. One Half the People: The Women's Fight for Suffrage., 1975